ANNOUNCER : Attention , boils and ghouls ,
it 's time for Dr. Wolfenstein 's
" Creature Feature Show . "
Ah-hhh .
The doctor is in .
Don 't scream . Don 't move .
Stay tuned for Channel 68 's
Halloween Eve movie marathon .
I 'm your host , your ghost host
with the most , Dr. Wolfenstein .
I will be with you
until the end .
Howdy folks . Black Blood .
Violence . Freaks of Nature .
Come on down to Captain Spaulding 's
Museum of Monsters and Madmen .
See the Alligator Boy .
Ride my famous Murder Ride .
Most of all , don 't forget to take home
some of my tasty fried chicken .
It just tastes so damn good .
( clucking )
SPAULDING : ... with a meat cleaver .
( laughing )
See it , hear it , and actually feel it .
Coming after you to rip your flesh apart .
( laughing )
Unbelievable but true .
See it , hear it , and actually feel it .
( laughing )
Shit , I can 't do nothin ' with this . I can 't get rid of this .
It ain 't worth nothin ' , my name 's all over it .
I was fixing it to trade it to Jackie Cobb .
That retard that hangs out at Molly 's Fruit Stand ?
- Yeah . - For the life of me
I cannot understand why you hang out with that asshole .
He 's one horny retard .
Well , ain 't they all ? All they wanna do is eat and fuck .
If you knew him , you might understand his urges .
Worse than a rabid-ass baboon .
You know what his favorite thing is next to whacking his weasel ?
He takes a sharpened pencil
and sticks it in his eyeball and twists it .
- What ? - He doesn 't hurt himself though ,
he kind of twists it right next to his eyeball .
He 'd been putting that pencil someplace other than his eyeball .
He don 't do nothin ' like that . Although , once he got caught
with a " Planet of the Apes " doll stuck up his asshole .
Goddamn .
They had to take him to the hospital .
Kid had Dr. Zaius stuck halfway up his butt .
Couldn 't get it out .
- Did you fix the toilet ? - Yes , I did ,
and I don 't want you stuffing any goddamn paper towels down there .
I had to snake the shit out that thing .
Here you go .
You bust that crapper and I 'm gonna bust your ass .
I hear ya .
Mary , fucking Moses , ya 'll get the fuck outta here .
Hold it , clowney . Keep your paws where I can see them .
GUNMAN # 2 : Don 't move . I 'll blast a hole the size of
a Kansas City watermelon through your ugly ass , Bozo face .
What the fuck is that supposed to mean ?
Go grab that other asshole out of the shitter
- and drag his ass back in here . - Right .
You miserable motherfu ... I ought to jump over this counter
and bash your fucking balls in .
All right , Tippy , hand over the cash box
and I might leave your brains inside your skull .
I 'll tell you what , Ski King ,
why don 't you just take your mama home some chicken
and then I won 't have to stuff my boot all up in ya ass !
I don 't like chicken !
And I hate clowns !
GUNMAN # 1 : Put that shit down . Put it down !
That is it !
I 'm gonna count to 10 and you 're gonna hand over all the cash ,
or I 'm gonna splatter your grease-paint mug
across the state line .
- One ... - Fuck yo mama .
- Two ... - Fuck yo sister .
What are we gonna do ?
I know you , you work at the hardware store , right ?
- Richard Wick , right ? - Shut your trap .
Quiet down , both of you !
- Three ... - Fuck yo grandma .
I remember now . All the guys made fun of you .
- Called you Little Dick Wick . - Shut up !
# Little Dick Wick played with his prick #
# Don 't his smell just make you sick ? #
Stop singing , I hate that song .
Put your fucking mask back on .
Fuck it !
Most of all , fuck you !
SPAULDING : Goddamn motherfucker got blood all over my best clown suit .
( man laughing )
# She got a corpse under her bed #
# She had her fun but now he 's dead #
# Her momma said , come feed desire #
# Her brother said , hey , throw her on the fire #
# This is the house #
# Come on in #
# Built on sin #
# This is the house #
# Nobody lives #
# You get what you give , yeah , yeah #
# I cut the flesh and make it bleed #
# Fresh skin is what I need #
# I let it dry out in the wood #
# All your crying did no good #
# This is the house #
# Come on in #
# Built on sin #
# This is the house #
# Nobody lives #
# You get what you give , yeah , yeah ... #
PREACHER : How many want to touch this afternoon ?
Raise your hand if you want God to touch you .
I 'm gonna pray that God will give you a divine touch ...
RADIO : ... the US Department of Agriculture
is checking whether state meat and poultry inspectors
are good enough to allow the product to go on sale nationally .
The USDA has said ...
Man , some of these Manson chicks are really hot .
Shit , how are we almost out of gas ?
And this squeaky , right here , now that 's a girl you would date .
- Jerry , how much did you put in ? - I don 't know ? Two , three bucks .
Two , three bucks ? I told you to fill ...
- Bill , feel me , am I made of money ? - Get off . Jesus Christ , Jerry .
Don 't panic yourself there way too much , caffeine guy .
I wouldn 't be drinking so much coffee
if you did your share of the driving .
- You know I don 't have nightvision . - Oh , not this again .
Seriously , I can 't even make out the lines in the road .
If you wanna pull the car over , I 'll be more than happy
to kill us out in the middle of nowhere .
Besides , there 's a billboard right there .
Captain Spaulding 's Museum of Monsters and Madmen .
- BILL : Awesome , great ! - JERRY : Fried chicken and gasoline .
Next exit , there you go , problem solved
and we didn 't have to freak out . It was a real big deal .
BILL : Dick .
All right .
I 'll pump the gas . Go inside and see if it 's worth checking out .
Okay , Mr. Cranky .
Holy ... crap !
You gotta see this place . It 's boss .
- How boss ? - Really fucking boss .
Like , wake up the chicks and break out the camera boss ?
Hell , yeah .
Wakey , wakey ! Eggs and bacon .
Hey , sweetie , come on .
Grab Mary and get your stuff and come on inside .
Bill and I found a kick-ass place . Come on , move , move !
Let 's go .
Come on , Sleeping Beauty , it 's time to go to work .
BILL : What 's in that case over there ?
JERRY : Hairless monkey .
Did you see the crocodile boy ?
How 'd you like to find that in your pants ?
- Excuse me , sir ? Howdy . - Hi .
I love this place . How long have you been running this place ?
Well , uhm ... How long 's a piece of string ?
I don 't know .
Too goddamn long , that 's how long .
Too goddamn long , that 's right .
Right , I hear that , but how long , actually ?
Oh , shit , I don 't know exactly .
I took over for my pa , right after the Duke damned Oscar .
- Oh , you mean John Wayne . - Hell , son .
How many dukes do you know about ?
- Greatest American ever lived . - Look at that .
" Circle up the wagons , pilgrims . "
" Whatever you say , cowboy . "
I 'm not that much of a Western fan .
I like science-fiction .
Ah-hhh . Space boy .
- ( beeping like robots ) - I figured as much .
Let me ask you something .
How come you 're asking so many jackassy questions ?
My friends and I , we 're driving across country
writing this book on off-beat roadside attractions ,
the crazy shit you see when you 're driving across the country .
I don 't drive cross country .
But if you did .
But I don 't .
Yeah , but supposing for a second that you did .
You little dickens , you .
I know what your problem is .
What 's that ?
Ya 'll think us folks from the country 's funny-like , don 't you ?
- Jerry ... - Well , saddle up the mule , ma .
Slide me some grits , I 's got to get me some education .
- Jerry ... - You asshole .
No , I 'm really very interested , I 'm not trying to make fun .
Gotcha !
You are such a bad clown .
Oh , fuck me , Side Sally ,
who the hell 'd wanna read about all this horseshit anyway ?
You 'd be surprised .
Son , look around .
Would I be surprised ?
Finally . Great , great . Come on , we paid for the tickets .
- Let 's go , let 's go , let 's go . - What tickets ?
This isn 't everything . There is actually a murder ride .
A murder ride ? I don 't want to go on a murder ride .
- Yes , you do wanna go on a ... - No , I don 't .
Hey , how about if we skip the murder ride ?
( mockingly ) Hey , how about if we go ?
CLOWN : Anytime this year , people . Tour is about to begin .
Okay , we 'll see you inside the murder ride , we 'll be back . Bye .
Ladies and gentlemen , boys and girls ,
children of all ages ,
you are about to enter the world of darkness ,
a world where life and death are meaningless ,
and pain is God .
- Pain ! - Billy , let 's go .
- Quit that , sport . - Sorry , Captain Spaulding .
We gonna have a good time now .
On your right , you will see
the infamous Albert ... Fish .
Masochist , sadist ,
child killer and most importantly ,
cannibal .
Mr. Fish , born 1870 and enjoyed spankings
with nail-studded paddles ,
stuffing needles deep into his groin .
- I have a question . How many ... - Hold all questions .
MAN 'S VOICE : No , no , help .
( woman screaming )
Lizzie fucking Borden .
Now , one of our most famous crazies ,
the psycho of Plainsfield , Mr. Ed Gein .
Murderer , cannibal ,
Mr. Gein used to take great pleasure
of playing with dead bodies of women ,
especially , their sexual organs .
( coyote howling )
Now , one of our local heroes ,
S. Quentin Quale ,
aka Dr. Satan .
Oh shit !
Murderer , torturer , but most of all , master surgeon .
Mr. Quail was an intern
at Willows County Mental Hospital ,
nicknamed Weeping Willows
for the neverending cries of pain .
Through primitive brain surgery ...
- Jerry , stop it . - Mr. Quail believed
that he could create a race of superhumans
from the mentally ill .
Vigilante justice prevailed .
They took his ass out and hung him .
( chuckles )
And that infamous hanging tree
is no more than a stone 's throw away
from where y 'alls ' ass is now seated .
But the next day
his body was found to be missing .
Until today
no trace of Dr. Satan
has ever been discovered .
But then , who knows ?
Maybe he lives next door to you .
Tour 's over . Exit through the doors .
That was so bad-ass .
Dr. Satan . Ah-hhh , Dr. Satan .
Maybe he lives next door to you .
Calm down , it was all right .
Do you think maybe we could go now ?
I 'm gonna go call my dad . I 'll be right back .
I love you .
What do you mean , it was all right ?
It was cool , but it wasn 't that great .
Dude , you don 't have to play it down in front of your chick .
- Oh . - Thank you .
- Don 't move a muscle , an artery , - ( phone ringing )
Or a vein .
- Hello ? - Hey , Dad .
- Wow , Denise . - We stopped for gas
at this place called Captain Spaulding 's ,
somewhere outside of Ruggsville .
It turned into this whole big thing , so we 're behind schedule .
Don 't be too late .
I forgot to tell you that Halloween falls on a school night
so they 're trick-or-treating tonight .
Your left hand shows your past ;
your right hand shows your future .
Good evening . I 'm Lance Brockwell
and this is the 7 : 00 news . And our top story tonight ,
investigators still have no leads to the strange disappearance
of the five cheerleaders from Ruggsville High School .
Cindy Thompson , Karen Murphy ,
Allison Cole , Valarie Green , and Dawn Baker
were last seen four days ago leaving a football game .
I know it seems stupid , but I really wanna see this tree .
Do yourself a favor , son , just forget about it .
Oh , come on , I live for this shit .
Okay , all right , I 'll draw you a damn map .
- Thank you . - I still say it 's a waste of time .
You are here . Go straight up this road .
Make the first right . First left .
Come straight across and down .
Can 't find it ? Tough .
- Here 's your map . - Right on .
- Here 's your complimentary chicken . - Oh , wow .
Don 't let the door hit you in the ass on the way out .
You 're gonna get a great write-up for this .
Here 's an idea , let 's just skip it . It 's probably nothing anyway .
Christ , Jerry , Bill is right , we can 't see anything .
What 's that ?
Hitchhiker .
- What ? Should we stop ? - We can 't leave her in the rain .
Stick her in the front if you wanna pick her up so bad .
So , uh ,
- where ya headed ? - I was just going home .
- Home , where 's that ? - A couple miles up the road .
- So , you live around here ? - Yeah .
Do you know where this Dr. Satan tree 's at ?
Yeah . You know where that 's at ? It 's right by my house .
- I can show you . - Really ?
- So , it is a real thing . - ( whispering ) Fuck you .
So , a tree ? Where 's it at ?
- What tree ? - MARY : Okay , this is crazy .
She obviously doesn 't know anything .
Oh , I know , I 'll show you where it 's at .
Whatever you need to do , you do it .
There is no wrong .
If someone needs to be killed , you kill ' em .
That 's the way .
( gun cocks )
Fuck .
I think we blew a tire .
- Oh poop . - Oh , hell .
At least we got that spare .
You filled it up like I asked , right ?
Yeah , yeah .
Okay , what if I forgot to put it back in the trunk ?
What would plan B entail ?
- Jesus Christ , Jerry . - Technically I did what you said .
Oh for fucking sake , Jerry , what 're we gonna do now ?
( Scottish accent ) I can 't rightly say if I know , me ladies .
Wait , I love this song .
DENISE : Would you turn the radio off , please ? !
God !
We can walk to my house from here .
What ?
My brother 's got a tow truck . He can come get your car .
- I 'll go , it 's my fault . - Forget it , I 'm going .
- No , Bill , I ... - You guys stay here .
There 's no sense in everyone getting drenched .
TV REPORTER : Returning to the news , local authorities still have no lead
in the mysterious disappearance of the five cheerleaders
from Ruggsville . The girls were last seen
leaving a cheering competition ...
ACTOR # 1 : It was loud enough to wake the dead .
- ACTOR # 2 : That 's an idea . - ACTOR # 3 : What is ?
Wouldn 't it be dramatic ? Supposing the people inside were dead ,
all stretched out with the lights quietly burning about them .
I 'm sure it would be very amusing .
MAN : Why you ask ? Why is not the question .
How ?
Now , that is a question worth examining .
How could I ,
being born of such
conventional stock ,
arrive a leader of the rebellion ?
An escapist from a conformist world , destined to find happiness
only in that which cannot be explained .
I brought you here for a reason .
But unfortunately , you and your sentimental minds
are doing me no good .
My brain is frozen ,
locked .
I have to break free
from this culture of mechanical reproductions
and the thick incrustations
dying on the surface .
Oh , Christ .
Fuck it .
( woman giggling )
These are all my dolls .
I used to chop their heads off and their arms
and stick them up on the wall .
The door 's locked , I gotta go around .
Just wait here .
( woman screams )
Jesus Christ ! Don 't do that .
You scared the shit out of me .
You ain 't seen nothing yet .
- Is your brother ready to go ? - Yeah , he already left .
- Come on , inside . - What ? He left ?
Come on and get toasty .
Don 't worry about it , he 's fine .
I just don 't understand why ...
What was that ?
What ? I didn 't hear anything .
Turn the radio off .
Now listen .
I still don 't hear anything .
I swear to God , I heard some weird ...
Turn on the headlights , see if something 's out there .
( women screaming )
Calm down , calm down .
Jesus H. Christ .
It 's the fucking tow truck guy .
So ,
you live alone here ?
I mean , just you and your brother ?
Nah , there 's a bunch of us around somewhere .
I think Otis is upstairs messing around or something .
You gotta have the marshmallows .
That 's what makes it fun .
Yeah , I guess .
You sure do a lot of guessing .
- Thank you . - You 're welcome .
Wow .
Look at him .
He must 've been going pretty fast to smash through that wall .
You sure are silly for a guy with glasses .
- I like that . - Okay , hey .
Need those to see , thank you .
How do I look ?
Terrific , really .
Tasty .
Ain 't the only thing tasty in this house .
Okay , okay .
I wonder what time ...
- it 's getting kind of late . - Don 't worry , sugar .
It ain 't past my bedtime
Are you flirting with me ?
What ? Oh , no .
( horn beeping )
Great ! They 're back .
Whoppie-fucking-do .
Excuse me ?
I gotta call my dad and tell him we 're gonna be late .
Can I use your phone , please ?
Hello ?
Ain 't got one .
- Oh , hi . - Goodness .
You really don 't have a phone ?
No .
I once had one back in ' 57 ,
but ...
I don 't quite remember . There 's nobody round here .
I feel like jaw-flapping at no more .
Do you think the guy with the tow truck could drive us to a phone ?
His name is Rufus , Rufus Jr .
But we all call him
- RJ . - Makes sense .
What do they call you , sweetie ?
I am Qualsnarg of the Crab Nebula .
But you humans can call me Jerry .
Jerry .
Baby , go on and see how RJ 's doin ' with these nice folks ' automobile .
Why don 't you just all make yourselves to home ?
What brings you kids way out here ?
Haven 't you got something better to do on Halloween
than wander around out in the sticks ?
I thought maybe we 'd take in a hoedown .
No , he 's just joking .
- You are ? - I 'm sorry , I 'm messing with you .
Shut up , dude .
Oh , I get it .
Y 'all just think you 're too good
for the simple pleasures of Halloween .
No , just a little too old .
Oh really ? I hope something changes your mind
someday .
- Mama , Tiny 's home . - What about RJ ?
He was gone before I seen him .
But Tiny saw him and said he said he was going down to the yard
to get a new wheel .
How long is that gonna take ?
Probably be back in a couple of hours .
A couple of hours ? What ?
Can 't Tiny drive us to a phone ?
Tiny ain 't got no car ,
he ain 't even got a bicycle .
Even though I know that you think it is childish ,
tonight is Halloween Eve ,
and to us
it is special .
So you are all invited to dinner .
I hope to Christ she don 't expect us to wear these things .
What ever it is , just do it .
The more we play along the faster we 'll get the hell out of here .
Now is not the time to make waves . Jerry .
You 'll have to forgive Tiny .
He can 't hear so much .
That poor baby .
It 's his daddy 's fault .
Earl wasn 't a bad man ,
he never hit me or nothing like that .
One day he just up and went devil on us all .
- What happened ? - He tried to burn down the house .
He said it was possessed by the spirits .
And Tiny was sleeping in the basement where the fire started .
But I don 't think Earl ever meant to harm us .
Tiny was badly burnt , his ears were destroyed
and most of his skin .
- Is that why he wears the mask ? - Yeah .
My baby boy gets shy around new people ,
but he 'll warm up to you ,
especially the girls .
He 's a real lady-killer .
# All the kids wanna sniff some glue #
# All the kids want somethin ' to do ... #
You 're gonna miss a good show tonight .
That 's your tough luck .
I thought you kids were all about team spirit .
You ain 't done fuck-all to cheer me up since you got here .
Give me a B. Give me an A.
Give me a B. Give me a Y.
What 's that spell ? What 's that spell ? !
What 's that spell ? !
Baby .
You 're damn right .
# All the kids want somethin ' to do #
# Now I wanna sniff some glue #
# Now I wanna have somethin ' to do #
# All the kids wanna sniff some glue #
# All the kids want somethin ' to do . #
Okay now . Everybody put on your masks .
Can 't very well eat our desserts with our everyday faces exposed .
Can we ?
Gosh , kid , put it on .
She ain 't gonna let any of us touch dessert
unless you 're wearing this damn thing .
Mrs. Firefly ?
Do you know anything about the legend of Dr. Satan ?
- BILL : Here we go . - Shut up .
I 'm not much for gossip and this and that ,
- but I have heard ... - I know all about
what you wanna know all about .
Otis .
I can 't believe you decided
to come down and join us .
And you brought Little Wolf .
Oh , my baby .
Oh my God .
It 's such a special night for me .
I don 't know
who told you your fairy fables about Dr. Satan .
We heard it from a Captain Spaulding
up the road at ...
That old bitch hog don 't know shit .
Tells this cute little tattle-tales to sell his junk ,
but he don 't sell no Yankee boys no truth .
Something happened , right ? It had to be based on some real incident .
Are you , Jimmy Olsen , cub reporter for the Daily Asshole ?
- Grampa , watch your language . - I don 't think you need to know .
Better you leave here with your head still full
of kitty cats and puppy dogs .
- I really would like to know ... - Hey , he 'd really like to know .
Enlighten him .
I bet you 'd stick your head in fire if I told ya you could see hell .
Meanwhile , you 're too stupid to realize
you got a demon sticking out your ass
singing , " Holy Miss Moley , "
ALL : " Got me a live one . "
Can we change the subject , please ?
Dinner 's over .
Ladies and germs ,
it 's show time !
Tell you a little story ...
Eat your wife 's pussy ...
I mean jam your face in it !
... starts licking and chomping on her pussy
and she 's screamin ' and yellin ' and she just ...
Ah-hhh !
The old battleaxe at home 's liable to crush my balls !
Would you be quiet ?
You 're gonna wake up grandma .
Bravo , man .
Hey , hey , hey , don 't be moving now , don 't be moving .
We got something real special for you men out there .
# I 'm not #
# One of a greedy kind ... #
- Wow ! - # All of my wants are simple #
# I know what 's on my mind #
# I 'm not #
# Resting until I find #
# What would make your eyes glisten #
# With joy #
# Now listen #
# Big boy #
# I wanna be loved by you , just you #
# Nobody else but you #
# I wanna be loved by you #
# Alone #
# Boop-boop-a-doop #
# I wanna be kissed by you , just you #
# And nobody else but you #
# I wanna be kissed by you #
- # Alone ... # - All right .
- DENISE : Jerry . - # Boop-boop , I couldn 't #
# Aspire #
- # To anything higher ... # - Get off him .
I said get the fuck off him , you stupid fucking whore !
- Fucking slut ! - You shouldn 't have done that .
Oh , really ? Are you gonna do something about it ?
- I 'll do something , motherfucker . - Yeah , come on .
I 'll fucking cut your tits off and shove them down your throat .
- Baby , stop ! - Come on , Ma ,
- this bitch has got it coming . - No , I told you , remember ?
- Car 's done . - Thank God .
I suggest that you kids leave .
We 're gone .
Fuck you !
- I love you , Mama . - I know .
- DENISE : Lock the fucking doors ! - MARY : Hurry up .
Jesus Christ , you think she was really gonna cut you .
Of course she was gonna cut me , she 's a fucking nut .
I knew she was crazy from the second we picked her up .
Okay . That 's that .
JERRY : Let 's get out of this fucking nuthouse .
( everyone screaming )
MARY : What 're you doing ? Why are you stopping ?
- I gotta open the gate ! - For Christ 's sake , hurry up !
Oh , shit !
( shouting )
MARY : Somebody help him !
- DENISE : Oh shit ! - MARY : What are they doing to him ?
MARY : Who 's that ?
DENISE : Oh my God !
- MARY : Shut the fucking door ! - DENISE : Oh , no !
Somebody help us !
Oh my God ! Get away from us !
No , please .
Oh my God !
No-ooo !
Help me ! Help me !
( Otis and Mary screaming )
RADIO : ... rock and roll this morning with some Led Zeppelin
kinda wild around the radio station today ,
it being a holiday .
It 's kinda like a ghost town around here .
It 's kinda nice though , it 's kinda kick back .
Maybe time to get away with stuff .
( telephone ringing )
Huston .
Donald Willis .
- Don Willis , how the hell are you ? - Listen , Frank ,
I 'm a little worried about Denise .
She called me last night from the road near Ruggsville ,
a place called Spaulding 's .
Yeah , I know the joint .
She said she 'd be here about 11 : 00 , but she never showed up .
I 'll run a check on up there by Spaulding 's
and see if there 's any accidents , or road closings .
It was raining like a son of a bitch here last night .
They 're probably just stuck in the mud someplace .
OTIS : Shut your mouth !
I said , shut your fucking mouth !
Listen , you Malibu middleclass Barbie piece of shit ,
I 'm trying to work here !
Work ! You ever work ?
Yeah , I 'll bet you have .
Scooping ice cream to your shitheel friends on summer break .
I ain 't talking about no goddamn white socks
with Mickey Mouse on one side and Donald Duck on the other .
I ain 't readin ' no funny books , Mama .
Our bodies come and go , but this blood is forever .
I 'm gonna remove your gag ,
but if you make so much as a fucking peep
I 'm gonna cut you like a pig
and make you eat your own fucking intestines . You got me ?
Why are you doing this to me ?
- Why are you doing this ? - Doing what ?
Messy up your day ?
Where 's Bill ?
- Where 's Bill ? - Bill ?
Is he okay ?
He 's a good guy .
He 's been a great help to me . A real blessin ' .
I couldn 't have asked for a better specimen .
You don 't know
what kind of dry spell I 've had ,
total block , total block .
But Bill ,
he 's okay .
Where is he ?
Hi .
# ... brick house #
# She 's mighty mighty , #
# Just lettin ' it all hang out #
# She 's a brick house #
# I like ladies stacked and that 's a fact #
# Ain 't holdin nothin back #
# Oh , she 's a brick house #
# Well , we 're together everybody knows , #
# This is how the story goes #
# She knows she 's got everything #
# That a woman needs ... #
Where is he ? Can I see him ?
Can I see Bill , please ?
Let 's go see .
Behold ...
- Fish-boy ! - Oh my God !
Oh my God , Bill .
No , no , this can 't be real . This can 't be real .
This can 't be real , this can 't be real .
Oh , it 's real .
Real as I want it to be , Mama .
Fuck you , you fucking freak !
# Whose gonna dry #
# Your big blue eyes #
# Day after day ? #
# Who 's gonna jump #
# When you say frog ? #
- # Who 's gonna bow ... # - Well ...
Let 's see if the nut that runs this place can help us .
Take a look at all this crap .
I 'd red flag anybody running a joint like this .
Sweet baby Jesus .
Whoever 's jerking off on that bell better be gone when I come out ,
or I 'm gonna rip your nuts off .
Officers , officers , what can I do for you ?
I ain 't fired up the birds yet
if that 's what you 've been ring-a-ding-dinging about .
I need you to answer some questions about some missing kids .
Oh , I don 't know nothin ' about nothin ' .
I 'm the kind of guy that just minds his own business ,
if you get what I 'm saying .
You seen this girl ? Say in the last 24 hours ?
Yeah , yeah , a cute kid .
Ain 't my type though .
I like ' em with a little more meat on ' em .
The bigger the cushion , the sweeter the pushin ' .
( Spaulding snorts )
Look , clown-ass , just answer the damn question .
We ain 't interested in your love life , all right ?
Cut the crap , Spaulding and get with the facts .
Huh ?
What did you see ? Who was she with ?
- Where was she going ? - I don 't know .
She was with some stupid kids . They 's nosing around ,
asking a bunch of stupid questions .
- Questions about what ? - I don 't know .
This and that . Mostly a bunch of tired Dr. Satan bullshit .
They caught a gander at the display in the back
and they figured they 's gonna run out
and solve the great Deadwood mystery .
And how 'd they get that idea ?
I wrote ' em a map .
Out to the old farm road .
I figured , what the hell ? It wouldn 't do no harm .
' Sides , it 's good for my tourist trade .
You can shit 10 bricks for all I care .
What else ?
Nothin ' .
Stupid-ass kids probably got themselves
turned around ass-backwards and got theyself lost .
Is that all ? And I want you to think real hard .
Well , I don 't rightly know .
They wasn 't here long enough for me
to get up close and personal with ' em ,
like I do most assholes that come wandering in here .
How about you write them same directions out for me then ?
All right , all right . Don 't get all " True Grit " on my ass .
You can knock yourself silly for all I care .
Enough talk ! Write .
I don 't know where that skunk ape sleeps .
All I know is , that he had impure relations with my wife .
That 's true , he performed lurid acts upon me and my person .
Hold up the picture .
I 'm gonna kill that skunk ape .
Please , Tiny . Please let me go .
Let me go . Help me .
Please , God , please .
Thank you . Thank you .
I 'm just gonna go now .
I 'm just gonna go home .
I 'm just gonna go home now .
I 'm just gonna go now .
I 'm just going home now .
Where the fuck do you think you 're getting to ?
No , no , no ...
Playtime is over .
( police radio chatter )
It matches .
Call it in .
- I think we found ' em . - Yeah .
Hey , poopie pants . What 's new ?
Where the fuck is Bill ? Where 's Denise ? You can 't keep us here .
Shut up !
Wanna play a guessing game ?
Guess what number I 'm thinking of .
Eat shit and die .
No , wait , please . Come on , stop it . What do you want from me ?
- What do you want from ... - Be quiet . I don 't wanna slip .
Okay , one more .
You get this right , I 'll let you go .
If you get it wrong , you are fucked !
Who 's my favorite movie star ?
I don 't know .
Marilyn Monroe .
No , Betty Davis . Sorry , you lose !
Ah-hhh !
Jesus , somebody had themselves a field day
beating the shit out this thing , didn 't they ?
Yeah .
No mercy shown here .
Didn 't find any bodies , did ya ?
- Not yet . - Holy Christ .
What could these kids have done to bring this much hell down on ' em ?
- I found something . - What 's that ?
Keys .
Don 't stand there like some prize dog , Dick , open the trunk .
- Yes , sir . - Toss them here .
- Oh , Goddamn . - DICK : You got something , Georgie ?
Yeah .
We found something .
OTIS : People come , people go ,
but how many ever stop to take a look
at the underbelly of the beast ?
I make ' em stop and I make ' em look .
Hope you like what you see .
Hope you like what you see !
Just hold it a minute , Grandpa .
GRANDPA MUNSTER : At a time like this , you 're taking pictures ?
HERMAN : I just couldn 't help it .
You look so natural sitting in that box .
Put me behind the wheel of that bitch , I 'll show you drivin ' .
You useless fuck . You couldn 't even get your big ass in that seat .
You ungrateful ...
Don 't start with me , Hugo .
Get off the damn car , this ain 't your living room .
Goddamn grease monkey .
You sure this guy is supposed to ride with us ... in this car ?
Mm-hmm .
This doesn 't seem right to me .
It ain 't up to us , Chief said pick him up and take him with us .
Guy 's an ex-cop , figures he can be of some help .
I just hope he doesn 't get in my way , is all I 'm sayin ' .
This must be him .
- Mr. Willis ? - Yes , sir .
- I 'm Wydell , this is Nash . - How you doin ' , sir ?
Donald Willis . Any leads ?
We were on our way out to check on a couple of farms
out on the edge of town .
That 's about our only lead up to this point .
What about this body you found ?
You know about that ?
Local girl . Karen Murphy .
One of the cheerleaders that went missing last week .
That 's it ?
We know the kids were on their way out
to a place the locals call Deadwood .
They wanted to play Nancy Drew with this local legend
people call Dr. Satan .
- This is insane . - Don 't you worry about it .
We 'll find her , all right ?
My name is Lewis Dover
and I 'm no rich man , but I know the truth .
You don 't have to go to hell .
You 're in hell ... this is hell .
This is hell . This is hell .
I 'm gonna see if anybody 's home . You and Mr. Willis
check around , see if you see anything .
Come with me .
( knocking on glass )
I hate fucked up families !
- It 's just a dip . - MAMA : Otis !
Otis , come quick . There 's cops out there .
- What ? Damn ! - How many ?
- Don 't worry about it . - I don 't know . I only saw one .
Fucking pigs always travel in packs .
- Take this . - What should I do ?
Go downstairs and play nice .
I 'll go round back and take control like I always fucking do .
Goddamn .
These packrats throw anything away ?
- I don 't think so . - Hold this thing .
Hello ? Hello ?
You 'd think these son of bitches would have a yard sale , don 't you ?
Yeah .
Hello ?
Oh my God !
- Oh my God ! - Calm down , Barney !
Don 't even start with that " Mayberry " shit .
It 's only a dog .
I was bit by a cocker spaniel when I was eight years old .
- Hello , Officer . - Good afternoon , ma 'am .
I 'm Lieutenant Wydell . I 'd like to ask you a few questions .
Why , heck , I 'll tell you anything you wanna know .
I appreciate the cooperation , ma 'am .
I 'm looking for a missing girl .
I 'm serious . It was a big cocker spaniel ... big teeth .
It was my ex-girlfriend 's . Almost bit off my pinky toe .
Yeah , yeah , yeah .
Shh , you hear that ?
Yeah .
Yeah , I hear it . Where do you think it 's coming from ?
Out this way .
All right , hold on , hold on one second here .
Hey , hey !
Sheriff 's Department , open up .
- No , I ain 't seen her , sorry . - Ma 'am ...
If I could just come in for a minute .
I have some other pictures I 'd like you to look at .
It might stir something up .
No . I don 't think so .
Ma 'am .
It 'll only take a minute .
Oh , all right .
I guess I can trust you ,
being a man of the law .
Yes , ma 'am .
Thank you , ma 'am .
# I remember you ... #
# You 're the one who made my dreams come true #
# A few kisses ago ... #
Oh , this one looks familiar . Is he on the TV ?
No , ma 'am , I don 't believe he is .
# You 're the one who said I love you too #
- Wydell ? - Excuse me , ma 'am .
- Wydell , over ! Wydell , over ! - Wydell , over .
# I remember #
# Two distant bells #
# And stars that fell #
# Like the rain out of the blue #
# When my life is through #
# And the angels ask me #
# To recall #
# The thrill of them all #
# Then I will tell them #
# I remember you #
# I remember #
# Two distant bells #
# And stars that fell #
# Like the rain #
# Out of the blue #
# When my life is through #
# And the angels ask me #
# To recall #
# The thrill of them all #
# Then I will tell them #
# I remember #
# Tell them I remember #
# Tell them I remember you . #
( dog barks )
( coyote howling )
Let me take a guess here . Y 'all havin ' a Halloween Party .
What makes you think that , big boy ?
You sure are buying a whole mess of holy water for two people .
We like to get fucked up and do fucked up shit .
- You know what I mean ? - I like to get fucked up too .
- Do some fucked up shit . - Yeah , I bet you do .
How much we owe ya , goober ?
Actually it 's G. Ober , for Gerry Ober ,
but the new guy , Romald in the back , he drew in that other O
and made Goober . Fucking asshole .
Great story , Goober . How much we owe ya ?
The damage is quite severe .
- $ 185 . - That ain 't gonna break my bank .
Here , keep the change and go get yourself a new name , Goober .
Holy dog , I will , thank you .
You all drive safe . Thanks for comin ' in to Red Hot Pussy Liquor .
Where 's Otis ? Where 's Otis ?
He 's comin ' . He 's got something real special this year .
RUFUS : Otis , Otis , Otis ...
OTIS : I 'm the one who brings the Christmas candy .
Now tell me ,
who 's your daddy ?
I 'm the one who brings the devil 's brandy .
Who 's your daddy ? !
I 'm the one who beats you when you 're bad .
- Who 's your Daddy ? ! - Who 's your Daddy ? !
Come on , sweetie , give the old man some sugar .
Daddy , Daddy .
And I 'm the one who loves ya
when you 're fucking dead .
Who 's your Daddy ? ! Who 's your Daddy ? !
Well , I say my little darlings .
Maybe it ain 't a good idea to be prancing around
where you don 't belong .
And you , the great rusher of fools ,
what was it that you were after ?
Come on , speak to me , boy . I remember now .
Dr. Satan .
Goddamn it , everybody got to know about Dr. Satan .
You know what I 'm gonna do ? I 'm gonna do you a favor .
I 'm gonna let you meet the old bastard .
It 's all true .
The bogeyman is real and you found him .
( echoing ) And you found him ...
Hey , happy boy , step your ass up here .
Take his gag out . It 's more fun with the screaming .
I like that too . That screaming is much more exciting that way .
Please don 't kill us , please don 't kill us .
Please don 't kill us ... nah ... please don 't kill us .
Shut your mouth and get your shit in the box .
- Get in now . - MAMA : Wait , wait , wait ...
I wanna say goodbye .
Goodbye , sweetie .
We could 've been great .
Just let us go , I swear to God we won 't tell anyone .
- I swear ... - Honey , you know I can 't do that .
BABY : I swear to God , we won 't tell . I swear to God .
Ain 't we just having a fucking hoot ?
RUFUS : Get your fucking ass up , boy .
OTIS : Come on , we ain 't got all night .
Where does she think she 's gonna run to ?
- She gonna run all the way home ? - No , let me get her .
All right , go get her .
Huntin ' humans , ain 't nothin ' but nothin ' .
They all run like scared little rabbits .
Run , rabbit , run .
Run , rabbit .
Run , rabbit . Run , rabbit .
Run , rabbit , run !
Run , rabbit !
BABY : There once was a woman
who lived with her daughter in a cabbage garden .
Along came a rabbit and ate up all the cabbages .
The woman said , " Go into the garden and drive out the rabbit . "
Mary .
Told you . I 'm gonna get you .
I 'm gonna get you . I 'm coming to get you .
( laughing )
( yelling )
( screaming )
" Shoo , shoo , " said the maiden .
" Come , maiden , " said the rabbit .
" Sit on my tail and go with me to my rabbit hutch . "
( Baby chuckles )
No-ooo , no !
No hanky-panky . Rufus , put the lid on .
No-ooo !
Oh , no !
No !
No , no , no !
Stop ! No !
No !
No-ooo !
No , no-ooo !
( coyote howling )
( distorted audio ) Bury me in a nameless grave .
TAPE : Bury me in a nameless grave .
Jerry , wake up , wake ...
Jerry , wake up , wake up , wake up .
Bury me in a nameless grave .
Oh my God !
- JERRY : No-ooo ! - Jerry !
No , Jerry !
JERRY : Please ! Help !
Help me !
I can 't see anything !
( echoing ) Jerry ? Is that you ?
( echoing ) Jerry ?
Jerry ? Thank God .
Please help me .
( siren wailing )
God !
( screaming )
Jerry ?
Oh , God , no , no , no ...
No !
( mumbling )
No-ooo !
No !
God , no , no .
No , no !
No-ooo !
( chanting )
( breathing heavy )
( heartbeat )
Go away !
Sweet baby Jesus , girl . What the hell happened to you ?
I got away .
I recognize you .
There 's a whole bunch of people been looking for your ass .
- I gotta get to a doctor . - All right , all right .
Just sit back and relax .
I 'll get you to a doctor .
Come on ... that 's it , that 's it .
I 'll get you there , yeah , yeah .
WOMAN : Oh , yeah !
( moaning )
# Ow , she 's a brick house #
# Yeah , she 's mighty mighty , just lettin ' it all hang out #
# That lady 's stacked , that 's a fact , #
# Ain 't holdin ' nothin ' back #
# Ow , she 's a brick house #
# Well put together , everybody knows #
# This is how the story goes #
# She knows she 's got everything #
# The woman needs to get a man #
# Ow , how can she lose #
# With the sex she use #
# 36-24-36 , what a winning hand #
# Ow , she 's a brick house #
# Yeah , she 's mighty mighty , just lettin ' it all hang out #
# That lady 's stacked , that 's a fact #
# Ain 't holdin ' nothin ' back #
# Ow , she 's a brick house #
# Well , she 's the one , the only one #
# Built like an Amazon #
# The clothes she wears , the sexy ways #
# Oh , they wish for younger days , well , well #
# She knows she 's built and knows how to please #
# Sure enough can knock a strong man to his knees #
# She 's a brick house #
# Yeah , she 's mighty mighty just lettin ' it all hang out #
# Ow , she 's a brick house #
# The lady 's stacked , that 's a fact #
# Ain 't holdin ' nothin ' back , ow #
# Shake it down , shake it now , now #
# Shake it down , shake it now , now , now , ow #
# Shake it down , shake it now , now , now , ow ... #
# Run , run , run ... #
# Run , run , run rabbit #
# Run away #
# Run , run , rabbit #
# Let me get it , I know what to do #
# Run away #
# A child so pure #
# Dyin ' in the clutch #
# Down in the hutch #
# Run , run , rabbit #
# Run away . #
Synchronization R.O.D.